Psalm
stop reading
Most people
at the cross.
twenty-two
going
Keep
end in a
doesn't
it
grave.
stay
doesn't
But the cry
forsaken.
Later,
turns
psalm
the
moves from
voice
the same
to praise:
anguish
name
thy
"I will declare
my brethren:
unto
of the
midst
in the
congregation
thee."
will I praise
voice?
praising
Who is that
line
that opening
Hebrews takes
and puts
word
word for
of
mouth
it in the
Christ.
the risen
turn is Jesus,
psalm's
The
side
on the far
alive
cross.
of the
He calls
what
And hear
us.
"not
says He is
Hebrews
brethren"
call them
ashamed to
brothers.
Family.
who cried
Jesus
The same
lives
now
out forsaken
is
Christ
and the risen
to call His
ashamed
not
brethren.
own
you into
calling
He is
family.
that